https://www.excelfcu.org/privacy-policy/

VIEW CURRENT RATES
Become a MemberReady to make it official? Join today!
Join Now!
Privacy Notice: Federal law requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.
Our privacy policy has not changed and you may review our policy and practices with respect to your personal information by clicking on the link below or we will mail you a free copy upon request by calling 770-441-9235 or toll-free at 1-888-441-9235.
Privacy Policy
Become a MemberReady to make it official? Join today!
Join Now!
Apply for a Loan
Privacy Policy
Fee Schedule
Disclosures
FollowFollow
Copyright © 2020 Excel Federal Credit Union. All rights reserved. Federally Insured by NCUA.
Our Accessibility Commitment
Excel Federal Credit Union is committed to making its banking products and services accessible to all of its members. We want everyone who visits our website to feel welcome and find the experience rewarding. Your experience is important to us.
If you are using a screen-reader or other auxiliary aid and are having problems utilizing this online or mobile application, please call our member support team at 888-441-9235 during normal business hours to discuss all of the same product and services information found in this online or mobile application. We will work with you to provide the information or item you seek through a communication method that is accessible to you.
You can also visit our branches during normal business hours.
Important Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel Continue
Important Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueImportant Message
You are now leaving EXCEL Federal Credit Union's website. You are linking to an alternate website that is not operated by the credit union. The credit union is not responsible for content on the alternate site. Privacy and security policies of the alternate site may differ from those practiced by the credit union.
Cancel    ContinueOnline Banking
Account Number
Forgot password? | Routing #261071548
